Hudson Valley District Council of Carpenters; Records apap049
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Hudson Valley District Council of Carpenters Records
1887-1990
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
apap049
17.52 cubic ft.
On November 14, 1946 the Carpenters' District Council of Ulster County and Vicinity was chartered. This council had local chapters in Kingston and Ellenville, New York. During the late 1940's local unions in the area began affiliating with the district council and eventually the district council, on May 4, 1949, was rechartered as the Hudson Valley District Council of Carpenters, the change of name more closely describing its jurisdiction. New local unions continued to be created, and independent local unions continued to affiliate with the district council. By the early 1950's the district council represented carpenters in Columbia, Delaware, Dutchess, Greene, Sullivan, and Ulster counties.
Collection X
Biographical / Historical
Throughout the late 19th and early 20th century local carpenter unions began to form in the Hudson Valley of New York State. The unions were split into six different district councils. The Kingston District Council of Carpenters was original founded in 1908. Since it only had two local unions, it dissolved in 1909 after the merger of the two locals. The Carpenters' District Council of Ulster County and Vicinity was formed on November 14, 1946. When this council changed its name to the Hudson Valley District Council of Carpenters on May 4, 1949, some local unions decided to create a separate Ulster County District Council. The Ulster County District Council was chartered on May 4, 1949 and its jurisdiction also included previous locals administered by the original Ulster County Council. The Susquehanna Valley District Council of Carpenters remained independent until May 1, 1955 when it surrendered charter to the Hudson Valley District Council of Carpenters. The Lower Hudson Valley District Council of Carpenters also surrendered its charter to the Hudson Valley District Council of Carpenters on April 1, 1957.
The Hudson Valley District Council of Carpenters Continued to grow in the mid-20th century. By 1974, the district had fourteen locals under its jurisdiction. The Council decided to consolidate the fourteen locals into three: Local 255 of Bloomingburg, Local 258 of Oneonta, and Local 265 of Saugerties. On June 13, 1983 the Council also established Local 245 of Oneonta for residential work.
Arrangement
This collection is made up of five series. The first series includes records relating to the Hudson VAlley District Council of Carpenters. The second series contains the documents of Local 255 of Bloomingburg. The third series includes the records of Local 258 of Oneonta. The fourth series contains records relating to the Locla Council 265 of Saugerties, and the fifth series contains the records of Local 245 of Oneonta.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
All items in this manuscript group were donated to the University Libraries, M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives, by the Hudson Valley District Council of Carpenters and its affiliated locals. The minutes of the District Council's meetings and some of the contracts were preservation photocopied as a part of the Harry Van Arsdale, Jr., Labor History Project, and these originals have been returned to the Hudson Valley District Council of Carpenters. The Hudson Valley District Council of Carpenters donated the records of Locals 255, 301, 574, 729, 1662, and 2967, and the records of the district council itself. The records of Locals 251, 306, 1075, 1175, 1560, 2161, and 2328, and the records of the Kingston District Council of Carpenters were put on deposit at the University at Albany by Carpenters Local 265. The records of Locals 245, 258, and 310 were loaned to the University by Carpenters Local 258, preservation photocopied, and the originals were returned to the local.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to this collection is unrestricted.
Scope and Contents
The records of the Hudson Valley District Council of Capenters contain minutes, contracts, dues ledgers, membership ledgers and other records that document the activity of union carpenters in the lower Hudson Valley of New York State from 1887 until 1989.
Labor unions--New York (State); Carpenters; Labor unions--History--20th century; Labor unions--History--19th century; Hudson Valley District Council of Carpenters
- Hudson Valley District Council of Carpenters, 1948-1981; 1; .4 cubic ft.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged alphabetically.
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains the records of the Hudson Valley District Council of Carpenters which was chartered on May 4, 1949 when the Ulster and Vicinity Council as well as some other Locals combined.New locals and independent locals continued to affiliate with the district council, and by the early 1950's the district council represented carpenters in Columbia, Delaware, Dutchess, Greene, Sullivan, and Ulster counties. The records include minutes of meetings of the district council, contracts, and bylaws. This series also contains printed matter and material related to jurisdictional disputes with other carpenters' district councils. Minutes, a few contracts, and some other material in this series have been photocopied, and the originals have been returned to the Council.
  - Agendas, Reports, and Correspondence, 1966-1968 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Agreement Between Carpenters Local 1150 and Miron Truss and Components Corporation, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Agreement with Construction Employers of the Hudson Valley and Construction Employers Labor Relations Association of New York State, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Agreement with Employers Engaged on Construction of the West Delaware Water Supply Project of the Board of Water Supply of New York City, 1960-1965 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Agreement with Hudson Valley Construction Employers Association and Tri-County Construction Associates, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Agreements with Associated General Contractors of America, New York State Chapter, 1965-1973 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Agreements with Associated General Contractors of America, New York State Chapter (Heavy and Highway Agreements), 1970-1976; 1978-1987 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Agreements with Catskill Mountain Contractors Association (Heavy and Highway Agreements), 1961-1964; 1967-1971 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Agreements with Construction Employees of the Hudson Valley, 1977-1990 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Agreements with Various Employers Associations, 1958-1968 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - By-Laws, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Directory, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Health and Insurance Benefits Plan, 1975-1985 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Jurisdictional Discussions Between District Councils, 1948-1955; 1960 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Local Unions Before and After Consolidation, 1970-1980 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Minute Book, 1966-1968 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Minutes (1 of 2), 1966-1969; 1974-1981 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Minutes (2 of 2), 1966-1969; 1974-1981 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Photograph of Dinner Tenderd by the District Council of Carpenters of New York City In Honor of William L. Hutcheson, 1952 September 20 (Flat-file 1)
  - Senate Select Committee on Improper Activities in the Labor or Management Field, Correspondence and Contracts, 1949-1953; 1957-1958 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Trade Autonomy, 1960-1970 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Local Council 255 of Bloomingburg, 1887-1989; 2; 12 cubic ft.
  This series contains the records of Local 255 of Bloomingburg. Local 255 was created in 1974 when the Hudson Valley District Council of Carpenters merged 14 locals into 3. Local 255 combined 6 of the 14 locals. These locals were; Local 301, Newburgh (organized July 1, 1887, chartered November 25, 1888); Local 574, Middletown (organized May 3, 1900, chartered 1900); Local 729, Liberty (chartered April 12, 1949); Local 1038, Ellenville; Local 2373, Monticello (chartered October 24, 1950); and Local 2967, Port Jervis (merged into Local 574).
  Prior to the creation of the Hudson Valley District Council of Carpenters, some of these locals belogned to other district councils. Locals 301, 574, and 2967 were originally part of the Lower Hudson Valley District Council until that council surrendered its charter on April 1, 1957.
  Locals 729, 1038, and 2372 were originally part of the Ulster and Vicinity Council. Local 729 had jurisdiction over building and construction work in the northern part of Sullivan County specfically while Local 1038 orignally had jurisdiction in Ellenville and Local 2372 had jurisdiction in Monticello.
  This series contains records relating to the locals that make up Local 255. These records include meeting minutes, membership ledgers, daybooks, and contracts. While Local 1038 and Local 2372 are part of Local 255, there are no records on those specific locals in this collection. This series also contains a single ledger book of dues records remains to document the history of Local 1662. Although the local is located in Goshen, which is near all the other unions that eventually merged into Local 255, Local 1662 is not listed in any of the tables as being a part of the predecessors. The local might have been independent, but it is likely that it was affiliated with some predecessor to the current district council.
  - Local 255 Dinner Journals, 1984-1986; 1989 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Local 255 Membership Ledger (1 of 6), 1976-1983 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Local 255 Membership Ledger (2 of 6), 1976-1983 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Local 255 Membership Ledger (3 of 6), 1976-1983 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Local 255 Membership Ledger (4 of 6), 1976-1983 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Local 255 Membership Ledger (5 of 6), 1976-1983 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Local 255 Membership Ledger (6 of 6), 1976-1983 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Local 255 Minutes, 1975-1979 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Local 301, Agreement with General Contractors and Builders Association of Newburg, New York, 1954-1955 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Local 301, Arbitration, 1924 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Local 301 Daybook, 1904-1909 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Local 301 Daybook, 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Local 301 Daybook, 1960-1961 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Local 301, "In Defense of the Carpenter" Letter by Carpenters in Newburg News, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Local 301 Membership Ledger, 1896-1898 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Local 301 Membership Ledger, 1898-1901 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Local 301 Membership Ledger, 1907-1908 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Local 301 Membership Ledger, 1909-1910 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Local 301 Membership Ledger, 1915-1916 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Local 301 Membership Ledger, 1919-1920 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Local 301 Membership Ledger, 1921-1922 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Local 301 Membership Ledger, 1923-1924 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Local 301 Membership Ledger, 1925-1926 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Local 301 Membership Ledger, 1929-1930 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Local 301 Membership Ledger, 1931-1932 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Local 301 Membership Ledger, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Local 301 membership Ledger, 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Local 301 Membership Ledger, 1939-1940 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Local 301 Membership Ledger, 1941-1942 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Local 301 Membership Ledger (1 of 2), 1942-1943 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Local 301 Membership Ledger (2 of 2), 1942-1943 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Local 301 Membership Ledger (1 of 2), 1944-1945 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Local 301 Membership Ledger (2 of 2), 1944-1945 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Local 301 Membership Ledger, 1945-1947 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Local 301 Membership Ledger, 1947-1949 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Local 301 Membership Ledger (1 of 9), 1949-1959 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Local 301 Membership Ledger (2 of 9), 1949-1959 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Local 301 Membership Ledger (3 of 9), 1949-1959 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Local 301 Membership Ledger (4 of 9), 1949-1959 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Local 301 Membership Ledger (5 of 9), 1949-1959 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Local 301 Membership Ledger (6 of 9), 1949-1959 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Local 301 Membership Ledger (7 of 9), 1949-1959 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Local 301 Membership Ledger (8 of 9), 1949-1959 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Local 301 Membership Ledger (9 of 9), 1949-1959 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Local 301 Membership Ledger (1 of 10), 1963-1976 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Local 301 Membership Ledger (2 of 10), 1963-1976 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Local 301 Membership Ledger (3 of 10), 1963-1976 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Local 301 Membership Ledger (4 of 10), 1963-1976 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Local 301 Membership Ledger (5 of 10), 1963-1976 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Local 301 Membership Ledger (6 of 10), 1963-1976 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Local 301 Membership Ledger (7 of 10), 1963-1976 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Local 301 Membership Ledger (8 of 10), 1963-1976 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Local 301 Membership Ledger (9 of 10), 1963-1976 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Local 301 Membership Ledger (10 of 10), 1963-1976 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Local 301, Minutes, 1889-1892 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Local 301 Minutes, 1891-1896 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Local 301 Minutes, 1900-1906 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Local 301 Minutes, 1906-1910 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Local 301 Minutes, 1913-1916 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Local 301 Minutes, 1916-1919 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Local 301 Minutes, 1919-1924 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Local 301 Minutes, 1956-1957 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Local 301 Minutes, 1965-1972 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Local 301 Minutes, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Local 301, Photographs, 1948; 1952-1953 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Local 574 Day Book, 1900-1907 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Local 574 Day Book, 1913-1918 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Local 574 Day Book, 1919-1921 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Local 574 Day Book, 1922-1925 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Local 574 Day Book, 1925-1929 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Local 574 Day Book, 1929-1934 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Local 574 Membership Ledger, 1902-1904 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Local 574 Membership Ledger, 1905-1906 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Local 574 Membership Ledger, 1907-1908 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Local 574 Membership Ledger, 1914-1915 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Local 574 Membership Ledger, 1916 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Local 574 Membership Ledger, 1917-1918 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Local 574 Membership Ledger, 1919-1920 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Local 574 Membership Ledger, 1921-1922 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Local 574 Membership Ledger, 1923-1924 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Local 574 Membership Ledger, 1925-1926 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Local 574 Membership Ledger, 1927-1928 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Local 574 Membership Ledger, 1929-1930 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Local 574 Membership Ledger, 1931-1932 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Local 574 Membership Ledger, 1933-1934 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Local 574 Membership Ledger, 1935-1936 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Local 574 Membership Ledger, 1937-1938 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Local 574 Membership Ledger, 1939-1940 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Local 574 Membership Ledger, 1939-1947 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Local 574 Membership Ledger, 1941-1942 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Local 574 Membership Ledger, 1943-1944 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Local 574 Membership Ledger, 1945-1946 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Local 574 Membership Ledger, 1946-1947 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Local 574 Membership Ledger, 1947-1948 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Local 574 Membership Ledger (1 of 4), 1948-1952 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Local 574 Membership Ledger (2 of 4), 1948-1952 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Local 574 Membership Ledger (3 of 4), 1948-1952 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Local 574 Membership Ledger (4 of 4), 1948-1952 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Local 574 Membership Ledger (1 of 6), 1956-1971 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Local 574 Membership Ledger (2 of 6), 1956-1971 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Local 574 Membership Ledger (3 of 6), 1956-1971 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Local 574 Membership Ledger (4 of 6), 1956-1971 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Local 574 Membership Ledger (5 of 6), 1956-1971 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Local 574 Membership Ledger (6 of 6), 1956-1971 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Local 574 Minutes, 1900-1903 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Local 574 Minutes, 1903-1908 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Local 574 Minutes, 1908-1915 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Local 574 Minutes, 1915-1926 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Local 574 Minutes, 1926-1930 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Local 574 Minutes, 1958-1972 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Local 574 Minutes, 1972-1974 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Local 729 Membership Ledger (1 of 2), 1949-1954; 1967-1974 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Local 729 Membership Ledger (2 of 2), 1949-1954; 1967-1974 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Local 2967 Membership Ledger, 1951-1973 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Report of the General Secretary of United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, 1919 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Local Council 258 of Oneonta, 1964-1978; 3; 0.2 cubic ft.
  This series contains the records of Local Council 258 of Oneonta. Local 258 was chartered in 1974 and combined four of the locals that made up the Hudson Valley District Council of Carpenters. These locals included Local 310, Norwich; Local 1600, Cannonsville; Local 1656, Oneonta; and Local 2448, Fleishmans.
  Originally, Locals 310, 1600, and 1656 were part of the Susquehanna Valley District Council of Carpenters. Their charter dates are unknown. Local 2448 was originally part of Ulster County and Vicinity and held jurisdiction over building and construction work in Ulster County, Greene County, and half of Delaware County. This local was chartered on March 12, 1949.
  While multiple locals made up Local 258, only records of the original Local 310 exist in this series. These records include membership ledgers and meeting minutes.
  - Local 258 Minutes, 1975-1978 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Local 310 Minutes, 1964-1974 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Local Council 265 of Saugerties, 1897-1984; 4; 4.72 cubic ft.
  This series contains the records of Local 265 of Saugerties. Local 265 was chartered in 1974 under the Hudson Valley District Council of Carpenters, and was made up of 5 of the 14 original locals. These locals included; Local 251, Kingston; Local 1075, Hudson; Local 1175, Kingston; Local 2161, Catskill; and Local 2328. This series also contains records of Local 306. The dues ledger of local 306 is the only surviving record of Associated Shipyard Workers Unions, Carpenters Local 306, of Kingston. Local 306 might have been affiliated with the Hudson Valley District Council of Carpenters, but whether or not this is true is unknown. All members in this ledger are listed as being initiated in the period 1940-1942, so this was likely a young local at the time. This series also contains records of Local 1560. The record is of the complete history of Local 1560 from its first meeting on April 14, 1903, until its last in 1909. When Local 1560 was organized there was already one other carpenters' local (number 251) in Kingston. In 1908, these two locals formed the Kingston District Council of Carpenters, but both this council and Local 1560 dissolved in 1909 upon the merger of Local 1560 into Local 251. Local 1175 was also originally a part of the Kingston council. Locals 1075, 2161, and 2328 were originally chartered in 1955 as part of the Hudson Valley District Council of Carpenters. This series contains membership ledgers, meeting minutes, daybooks, correspondence and registers.
  - Local 251 Correspondence, 1909-1919; 1933; 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Local 251 Day Book, 1904-1909 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Local 251 Day Book, 1922-1924 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Local 251 Day Book, 1924-1926 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Local 251 Day Book, 1929-1930 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Local 251 Day Book, 1936-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Local 251 Day Book, 1938-1940 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Local 251 Day Book, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Local 251 Day Book, 1945-1946 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Local 251 Membership Ledger, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Local 251 Membership Ledger, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Local 251 Membership Ledger, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Local 251 Membership Ledger, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Local 251 Membership Ledger, 1940-1941 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Local 251 Membership Ledger, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Local 251 Membership Ledger, 1909-1910 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Local 251 Membership Ledger, 1911 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Local 251 Membership Ledger, 1914-1915 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Local 251 Membership Ledger, 1918 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Local 251 Membership Ledger, 1919 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Local 251 Membership Ledger, 1921 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Local 251 Membership Ledger, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Local 251 Membership Ledger, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Local 251 Membership Ledger, 1927 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Local 251 Membership Ledger, 1928 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Local 251 Membership Ledger, 1929 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Local 251 Membership Ledger, 1930 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Local 251 Membership Ledger, 1931 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Local 251 Membership Ledger, 1932 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Local 251 Membership Ledger, 1933 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Local 251 Minutes, 1897-1903 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Local 251 Minutes, 1902-1905 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Local 251 Minutes, 1905-1910 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Local 251 Minutes, 1908-1909 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Local 251 Minutes, 1910-1914 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Local 251 Minutes, 1914-1919 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Local 251 Minutes, 1919-1923 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Local 251 Minutes, 1923-1927 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Local 251 Minutes, 1928-1930 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Local 251 Minutes, 1930-1933 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Local 251 Minutes, 1933-1937 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Local 251 Minutes, 1945-1953 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Local 251 Minutes, 1953-1962 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Local 251 Minutes, 1962-1966 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Local 251 Minutes, 1966-1974 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Local 265, Statement Made by Kenneth Rice at Catskill Peoples Committee For Progress Forum on the Prattsville Project, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Local 306 Membership Ledger, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Local 1075 Minutes, 1932-1937 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Local 1075 Membership Ledger, 1938-1950 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Local 1075 Minutes, 1937-1941 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Local 1175 Membership Ledger, 1943-1947 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Local 1175 Minutes, 1942-1945 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Local 1175 Minutes, 1945-1955 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Local 1175 Minutes, 1955-1962 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Local 1175 Minutes, 1962-1966 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Local 1175 Minutes, 1966-1972 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Local 1175 Minutes, 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Local 1560 Minutes, 1903-1909 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Local 1662 Membership Ledger, 1928-1949 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Local 2161 Minutes, 1965-1974 (Oversize 1)
  - Local 2328 Minutes, 1955-1958 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Local 2328 Minutes, 1958-1974 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Ulster, Sullivan, Delaware, and Green Counties Building and Constructing Trade Council, 1968-1974 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Local Council 245 of Oneonta, 1983-1990; 5; 0.2 cubic ft.
  This series contains the records of Local 245 of Oneonta which was chartered as part of the Hudson Valley District Council of Carpenters on June 13, 1983 for residental work. This local does not have any predescessors. This series contains meeting minutes of the local.
  - Carpenters Local 258 and 245 Dinner Dance Honoring General Patrick J. Capbell, 1987 February 28 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Minutes, 1983-1989 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Residential Construciton Agreement Between Construction Employees of the Hudson Valley Inc. and Hudson Valley District Council of Carpenters, 1985-1990 (Box 1, Folder 3)